Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Buttons and Memorabilia Collection, 1940-1990 IBT0057
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Gift of Regina Gormley, 1913-2001; 1940-1970; Series 3
  - William Gormley Delegate to the 8th Area IBT Conference, Atlantic City NJ Medal, 1966; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 281)
  - William Gormley Delegate to the ALA Founding Conference, Washington DC Medal, 1969; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 282)
  - Delegate to the 9th Area IBT Conference, Washington DC Medal, 1970; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 283)
  - William Gormely Delegate to the 20th IBT Convention, Miami Beach, FL Medal, 1971; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 284)
  - Local 633, Washington DC, Embroidered Teamsters Logo Patch, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 285)
  - Letter from Regina Gormley to Dennis Crean documenting gift of objects, 2003; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 286)
- Miscellaneous Acquisitions, 1872-2013; Series 4
  Series organized into six subseries: Buttons, Lapel Pins, Material Collected by Hollis Hypes, Material Collected by Sue Mauren, Miscellaneous Memorabilia Items, and Textiles and Associated Materials.
  This series consists of political and dues buttons, lapel pins, miscellaneous small memorabilia items such as keychains, and textiles, including an IBT vest, flag, and 2013 Women's Conference shirt and tote bag. Some of these items were acquired through small donations, while others were purchased.
  - Buttons, 1936-2001; 1939-1953; Series 4 Subseries 1
    Organized in approximate chronological order
    - Local 544 (Nov 1936) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Local 544 (Jun 1937) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Local 544 (Sep 1937) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 3)
    - Local 544 (Oct 1937) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Local 544 (Jan 1938) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 5)
    - Local 544 (Apr 1938) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 6)
    - Local 544 (Oct 1938) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 7)
    - Local 249 10th Anniversary (Dec 1938) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 8)
    - Local 544 (Jan 1939) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 9)
    - Local 544 (Apr 1939) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 10)
    - Local 584 Milk Drivers Protective (Jan 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 11)
    - Local 206 Warehousemen (Feb 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 12)
    - Local 676 (Feb 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 13)
    - Local 255 Garage & Service Station Employees (Mar 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 14)
    - Local 544 (Mar 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 15)
    - Local 305 Dairy, Ice, & Ice Cream Employees (Apr 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 16)
    - Local 404 Springfield (Apr 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 17)
    - Local 900 (Apr, May, Jun 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 18a-b)
    - Local 523 (Apr 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 19)
    - Local 128 Taxicab Drivers & Garage Employees (May 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 20)
    - Local 317 (May 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 21)
    - Local 6 Joint Council Brewery Workers (Jun 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 22)
    - Local 249 (Jun 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 23)
    - Local 340 (Jul 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 24)
    - Local 358 Laundry & Dry Cleaning Drivers (Sep 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 25)
    - Local 93 Milk Drivers & Dairy Employees (Sep 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 26)
    - Local 601 Beer Drivers, Distributors & Helpers (Sep 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 27)
    - Local 108 City Sanitary Drivers & Helpers (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 28)
    - Local 149 Lumber, Building Materials & Supply Drivers, Chauf. & Helpers Union (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 29)
    - Local 103 Oil Wagon D. C. & H. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 30)
    - Local 850 Commission House Drivers & Employees (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 31)
    - Local 100 (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 32)
    - Local 793 Funeral & Liv. Chauff. & Helpers (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 33)
    - Local 998 Garage & Parking Lot Employees (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 34)
    - Local 114 Bakery-Pie-Cracker & Yeast Dr. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 35)
    - Local 152 Soft Drink & Mineral Water Dr. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 36)
    - Local 127 Railway Express Drivers & Chauffeurs & Helpers (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 37)
    - Local 140 Furniture, Piano & Express Drivers & Helpers (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 38)
    - Local 172 Tea & Coffee D. & C. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 39)
    - Local 193 (Oct 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 40)
    - Local 883 (Oct 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 41)
    - Local 980 Filling Station, Garage & Parking Lot Emp. (Nov 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 42)
    - Local 816 (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 43)
    - Local 641 (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 44)
    - Local 677 Waterbury (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 45)
    - Local 161 Dept. Store Dr. & Chauff. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 46)
    - Local 98 Ice Cream Dr. Un. (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 47)
    - Local 544 (Dec 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 48)
    - Local 563 (Aug 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 49)
    - Local 563 (Oct 1940) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 50)
    - Local 710 Highway Drivers, Helpers & Platform Workers (Jan, Feb, Mar 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 51)
    - Local 292 (Jan 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 52)
    - Local 544 (Feb 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 53)
    - Local 544 (Apr 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 54)
    - Local 485 Bakery Drivers Union (May 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 55)
    - Local 369 (May 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 56)
    - Local 384 (May 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 57)
    - Local 563 Construction & General Laborers' (May 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 58)
    - Local 897 (Aug 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 59)
    - Local 617 (Sep 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 60)
    - Local 156 Taxicab Drivers (Sep 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 61)
    - Local 27 (Oct 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - Local 563 Construction & General Laborers' (Nov 1941) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - Local 609 Refuse Drivers & Collectors (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 64)
    - Local 236 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 65)
    - Local 359 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 66)
    - Local 88 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 67)
    - Local 462 Dairy Employees Union (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 68)
    - Local 441 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 69)
    - Local 536 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 70)
    - Local 597 (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 71)
    - Local 1113 Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers of Amer. (Jan 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 72)
    - Local 872 (Feb 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 73)
    - Local 694 (Feb 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 74)
    - Local 991 (Feb 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 75)
    - Local 110 (Mar 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 76)
    - Local 198 (Apr 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 77)
    - Local 147 (Mar 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 78)
    - United Farm Equipment Workers of America (Mar 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 79)
    - Local 926 Parking Lot Attendatns & Garage Employees (Mar 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 80)
    - Local 613 (Apr 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 81)
    - Local 840 Vandalia, Ill. (Apr 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 82)
    - Local 585 (Apr 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 83)
    - Local 182 Utica, NY (Jul 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 84)
    - Local 426 (Nov 1942) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 85)
    - Local 563 Construction & General Laborers' (Jan, Feb, Mar 1943) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 86)
    - Local 116 (Feb 1943) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 87)
    - International Association of Machinists Bunker Hill Lodge 634 (May 1943) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 88)
    - Local 600 (Feb 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 89)
    - Local 557 (Feb 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 90)
    - Local 685 (Feb 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 91a-b)
    - Local 929 Produce, Poultry, Fish & Oystermen Drivers & Helpers (Mar 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 92)
    - Local 491 (Jul 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 93)
    - Local 478 (Sep 1944) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 94)
    - Affiliate of Victoria & District Trades & Labor 3rd Quarter Council 1944 Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 95)
    - Local 343 (Mar 1945) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 96)
    - Local 343 (Mar 1946) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 97)
    - Local 429 Reading, PA (Sep 1946) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 98)
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees (Apr, May, Jun 1950) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 99)
    - United Farm Equipment & Metal Workers (1949) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 100)
    - Local 313 (Apr, May, Jun 1947) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 101)
    - Official Truck Check (1950) Button, 1936-2001; 1939-1953; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 102)
    - Minnesota Licensed Chauffeur (1951) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 103)
    - Minnesota Licensed Chauffeur (1953) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 104)
    - United Food & Commercial Workers International Union (Jan 1980) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 105)
    - United Food & Commercial Workers International Union (Oct, Nov, Dec 1994) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 106)
    - "Your Best Bet" 1986 IBT Election Pin w/ Candidate Portraits, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 107)
    - "Re-Elect Jim Hoffa" (2001) Button, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 108)
    - Local 638 Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 109)
    - "The Union is You" Local 116 Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 110)
    - Hercules Foundries Inc. Local 450 Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 111)
    - Teamsters Logo Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 112)
    - "I Back GE Strikers" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 113)
    - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 114)
    - "Shop Steward" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 115)
    - "I'm a Phenomenal Woman!" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 116)
    - "Teamster Women Make a Difference" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 117)
    - "Teamster Women" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 118)
    - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 119)
    - "Teamster Sisters - Yesterday, Today & Tomorrow" Button, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 120)
    - Local 99 Shield-Shaped Badge, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 121)
    - Teamster Logo Poker Chip Buttons, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 122a-b)
    - Vote Union Yes (UFCW) Buttons, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 123a-f)
    - "Int. Bro. of Teamsters" Truck Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 124)
    - "DRIVE to Survive" Truck Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Item 125)
    - IBT 24th International Convention Buttons, 1991; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 53a-d)
    - Local 544 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1992) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 54a-c)
    - Local 544 (Apr, May, Jun 1993) Button, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 55a-c)
    - Local 544 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1993) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 56a-c)
    - Local 544 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1993) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 57a-c)
    - Local 544 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1995) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 58a-c)
    - Local 544 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1995) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 59a-c)
    - Local 544 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1996) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 60a-c)
    - "Teamsters Vote Hoffa/Keegel '96" Button, 1996; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 61)
    - "Hoffa '96 Restore the Power" Button, 1996; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 62)
    - "Vote Hoffa/Slate (98)" Buttons, 1998; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 63a-c)
    - Local 120 (1999) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 64a-c)
    - "Gore/Lieberman 2000" Button, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 65)
    - Local 120 (2000) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 66a-c)
    - Local 120 (2001) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 67a-c)
    - Local 120 (2002) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 68a-c)
    - Local 120 (2004) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 69a-c)
    - "Si Se Puede - J. Gilberto Soto" Memorial Button, 2004; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 70)
    - "Hoffa 2006" Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 71a-c)
    - Local 120 (2008) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 72a-c)
    - Local 120 (2011) Buttons, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 73a-c)
    - "I'm with Hoffa" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 74)
    - Local 682 (2011) Button, Series 4 (Box 9, Item 75)
    - Local 71 "Chicago Newspaper Guild - No Contract No Peace" Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 76a-b)
    - "Let Hoffa Run!" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 77)
    - "Teamster Women - Working, Helping, Educating, Achieving Together" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 78)
    - "Mourn for the Dead, Fight for the Living" Workers Memorial Day Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 79a-b)
    - "Teamster Sisters - Yesterday, Today & Tomorrow" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 80)
    - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Pink Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 81)
    - "Diversity Matters" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 82)
    - "Organizing, Organizing, Organizing" Central Conference of Teamsters Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 83a-b)
    - Teamsters Joint Council 32 "Union Proud" Bald Eagle Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 84)
    - "Vote Teamster" Rainbow Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 85)
    - "Mark Dayton for Minnesota" Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 86)
    - "Vote Teamsters" Neon Green Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 87)
    - Ulysses S. Grant Replica Portrait Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 88a-b)
    - Grover Cleveland Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 89a-b)
    - William Jennings Bryan Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 90a-b)
    - William McKinley Replica Campgain Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 91)
    - Theodore Roosvelt Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 92)
    - Taft and Sherman 1912 Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 93a-b)
    - Woodrow Wilson Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 94)
    - Warren G. Harding Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 95a-b)
    - Calvin Coolidge Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 96)
    - La Follette/Wheeler Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 97)
    - Herbert Hoover Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 98a-b)
    - Al Smith Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 99)
    - Franklin Roosevelt Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 100)
    - Alfred Landon Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 101a-b)
    - Alfred Landon Replica Sunflower Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 102a-b)
    - Wendell Lewis Willkie Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 103a-b)
    - Thomas E. Dewey Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 104a-b)
    - Truman and Barkley Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 105)
    - Estes Kefauver Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 106a-b)
    - "I Like Ike" Replica Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 107)
    - Adlai Stevenson Replica Campaign Buttons, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 108a-b)
    - John Kerry Presidential Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 109)
    - John Kerry Senate Campaign Button, Undated; Series 4 (Box 9, Item 110)
  - Lapel Pins, ca.1900-2011; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - Teamsters Quebec (1999) Lapel Pin, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 126)
    - "The Voice of American Labor" Teamsters Vote 2000 Lapel Pin, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 127)
    - "100 Years" Teamsters Logo Pin, 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 128)
    - Local 399 75th Anniversary Lapel Pin, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 129)
    - Hoffa/Johnson Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 130)
    - Hoffa/Sweeton 27th Convention Lapel Pin, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 131a-e)
    - Hoffa/Johnson 2006 Lapel Pin, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 132)
    - Joint Council 25 Lapel Pin, 2011; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 133)
    - Local 104 AZ State Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 134)
    - Teamsters Quebec Local 106 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 135)
    - Local 710 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 136)
    - Local 135 Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 137)
    - Local 710 White UPS Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 138)
    - Local 710 Brown UPS Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 139)
    - Freight Member 710 Yellow Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 140)
    - Freight Member 710 Roadway Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 141)
    - Freight Member 710 USF Holland Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 142)
    - Freight Member 710 ABF Green Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 143)
    - Local 710 City Skyline Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 144)
    - Local 728 State of Georgia Movie Crew Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 145)
    - Local 916 Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 146)
    - Local 528 SEIU Racetrack & Gaming Workers United Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 147)
    - Local 1 "Stronger Together" SEIU Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 148)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 149)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers "Loyalty" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 150)
    - British Columbia Carpenters Union Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 151)
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees Red/White/Green Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 152)
    - I.P.P. & A. U. NY Printer's Union #51 Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 153)
    - Local 620 Carpenter's Union, Madison NJ, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 154)
    - Carpenters D.C. Central New Jersey Mosquito Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 155)
    - New Jersey Regional Council of Carpenters Skills Competetion 2008 Lapel Pin, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 156)
    - New Jersey State Council of Carpenters Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 157)
    - Eastern Conference of Teamsters Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 158)
    - Teamsters Freight Division Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 159a-b)
    - Teamsters Canadian Freight Divison Maple Leaf Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 160)
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employee Division of IBT Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 161)
    - IBT Warehouse Division Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 162)
    - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Rosie the Riveter Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 163)
    - International Teamster Women's Caucus Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 164)
    - "A Friend of Hoffa" Truck Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 165)
    - Teamsters Logo Gold Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 166a-b)
    - Teamsters Logo/Canadian Maple Leaf Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 167)
    - Teamsters Logo "50 Years" Lapel Pin from Bastian/crdl, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 169)
    - Bastian Brothers Teamsters Logo Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 169a-g)
    - Teamsters Logo W/ Regional Divisons Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 170a-c)
    - Small IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 171)
    - Gold IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 172)
    - Oval IBT Logo Lapel Pins, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 173a-b)
    - Jeweled IBT Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 174)
    - National Safety Council 3 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 175a-c)
    - National Safety Council 4 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 176)
    - National Safety Council 5 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 177a-b)
    - National Safety Council 6 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 178)
    - National Safety Council 7 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 179)
    - National Safety Council 8 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 180)
    - National Safety Council 9 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 181)
    - National Safety Council 10 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 182)
    - National Safety Council 12 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 183)
    - National Safety Council 13 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 184)
    - National Safety Council 14 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 185a-b)
    - National Safety Council 15 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 186)
    - National Safety Council 17 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 187)
    - National Safety Council 30 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 188)
    - National Safety Council 32 Year Safe Driver Award Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 189)
    - "Nat'l Fed. P.O. Motor Vehicle Employees" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 190)
    - "New York Post Office H.N.S." Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Item 200)